we're going to look at spring
我们要看春天
integration as a way of integrating
整合是整合的一种方式
otherwise to spare two data sources and
否则，将保留两个数据源，并且
services and spring irrigation of course
服务和春季灌溉
draws its inspiration from the the
从中汲取灵感
amazing book by Bobby hoping and Gregor
鲍比·霍普和格里高尔的精彩著作
Wolff called patterns of enterprise
沃尔夫称企业模式
application integration and the whole
应用程序集成和整体
point of the framework is to enable
该框架的重点是使
integration of otherwise disparate
整合原本完全不同的
services and data source rise it data
服务和数据源提升数据
sources okay so it's a it's it's all
资料来源还不错，就这样，就这样
about making things that don't
关于做不做的事情
necessarily know how to talk to each
一定知道如何与每个人交谈
other talk to each other and the easiest
对方互相交谈，最容易
way to do this is to think about the
做到这一点的方法是考虑
world in terms of events right or
就事件而言，世界还是
messages so perhaps I want to I want to
消息，所以也许我想要我想要
observe files on a file system and as
观察文件系统上的文件
soon as there's a new file I'm gonna
一旦有一个新文件，我就要
publish an event and then we spawn to
发布事件，然后我们生成
that right or maybe I want to observe
那个权利，或者我想观察
emails and in an inbox where I'm able I
电子邮件和收件箱中
want to observe you know new records add
想观察您知道新记录添加
it to a data source a database right or
将其发送到数据源，数据库权限或
or anything else these things are are
或这些东西是什么
all sorts of different you know these
各种各样的不同，你知道这些
these all implies different API and
这些都暗示着不同的API，
different technologies but with spring
不同的技术，但春天
integration that the the underlying
整合表明底层
details are hidden for you so now you
细节为您隐藏了，所以现在您
can think about it as just being a
可以认为它只是一个
message that gets published and there's
消息被发布，并且有
an adapter that that will publish the
一个适配器，它将发布
message for you right obviously you have
给您的消息，显然您有
to plug that in but spring negation
插入，但春天的否定
comes with a whole toolbox full of
带有一个完整的工具箱
innovation innovation adapters and then
创新创新适配器，然后
once the message is published you have
消息发布后，您将拥有
the the ability to then process that
然后处理的能力
message right to take it and do
接受并执行消息的权利
interesting things with it perhaps you
有趣的事情也许你
want to perpetuate it on and transform
想要延续下去并转型
the payload or they or the metadata
有效载荷或它们或元数据
about that message called the editors
关于称为编辑的消息
maybe you want to split it up into you
也许你想把它分成你自己
know numerous smaller messages maybe
知道很多小的消息
want to selectively route the messages
想要有选择地路由消息
based on some sort of condition to
根据某种条件
another component maybe want to do the
另一个组件可能想要
opposite of splitting maybe want to in a
与拆分相反，可能想要
downstream component when I a great the
当我很棒的时候
results of the split into one message
拆分成一条消息的结果
and then perpetuate that message
然后使该信息永久存在
downstream so you have you know a lots
下游，所以你知道很多
of different things you can do with a
您可以用
message once you've once you've seen it
看到消息后立即发送消息
once it's been published and finally
一旦发布，最后
when you have the message you can then
收到消息后，您便可以
send it to a downstream component like a
将其发送到下游组件
like an adapter or a gateway right so
像适配器或网关一样
instead of adapting the data as it comes
而不是适应数据
in you can take the message
在你可以接受消息
adapted to be to send it out right to
适于将其发送给
send it out to the to something in the
将其发送到
outside world so maybe they maybe the
外面的世界，所以也许他们也许
the the genesis of the message
信息的起源
processing flow came from a file in a
处理流程来自一个
file system but maybe as a result of
文件系统，但可能是由于
that processing you would like to upload
您要上传的处理
something to an FTP server right or
FTP服务器上的内容，或者
maybe you want to send a message on a
也许您想在
name QP rabbitmq broker for example
例如，以QP Rabbitmq经纪人的名字
right these are all distinct
对，这些都是截然不同的
possibilities but by by writing your
可能性，但是通过写你的
code with spring Novation you can use
您可以使用Spring Novation编写的代码
one component model and then you know
一个组件模型，然后您知道
compose stronger more powerful solutions
撰写更强大，更强大的解决方案
out of these smaller singly focused sort
从这些较小的单独关注的类别中
of components so let's take a look at
组件，所以让我们看一下
that today we're going to actually go
今天我们要去
back to that alluded to example or we're
回到提到的例子，否则我们
going to build an integration that
要建立一个整合
monitors a directory full of files and
监视充满文件的目录并
then takes the the files and then
然后取出文件，然后
process them processes them in some way
处理它们以某种方式处理它们
and then uploads them to an FTP server
然后将它们上传到FTP服务器
and I happen to have a an FTP server
我碰巧有一个FTP服务器
here on my machine so I'm going to say
在我的机器上，所以我要说
FTP sorry files - files and what we're
FTP抱歉的文件-文件以及我们所需要的
going to do file monitor files
要做文件监控文件
integration ok so we're going to call
集成好，所以我们要打电话给
that and I'm going to bring in a new
那我要带一个新的
piece support we'll bring that in here
件支持，我们将其引入此处
we're going to bring in spring
我们要带来春天
integration right so there's the
整合正确，所以有
integration support here as well we need
我们也需要这里的集成支持
to we need them the I think that'll do
我们需要他们，我想那会做
actually that that should be enough for
实际上，那应该足够
now we're gonna have to bring in some
现在我们要带一些
individual spring integration modules
单个弹簧集成模块
for her files and for FTP but that that
为她的文件和FTP，但那
should do us so let's go ahead and hit
应该这样做，所以让我们继续前进
generate and we'll get a zip file is the
生成，我们将获得一个zip文件
file we can open up in our ID and it
我们可以在ID中打开文件
really doesn't you know it doesn't
你真的不知道吗
matter which IDE as usual so I'm going
不管是哪个IDE，所以我要去
to say files integration what I want to
说文件集成我想要
do is I'm going to I want to monitor a
我要做的是要监视一个
directory and then if there's a new file
目录，然后如果有新文件
net directory I want to take that file
我要获取该文件的净目录
and I want to transform it in some way
我想以某种方式改变它
and then I want to send the transformed
然后我要发送转换后的
data to to a downstream system in this
数据发送到下游系统
case a an FTP server so we're going to
一个FTP服务器，所以我们要
build an integration flow using the
使用
spring integration Java configuration
Spring集成Java配置
DSL so we have that now because of
DSL，因为
spring boot 1.4 that's included in the
Spring Boot 1.4包含在
spring
弹簧
starter integration dependency so here
入门集成的依赖性，所以这里
it is right here and I think the Java
就在这里，我认为Java
DSL is one of the coolest things that's
DSL是最酷的事物之一
ever happened it's pregnan and i say
曾经发生过，这是pregnan，我说
that as a guy who's worked on spring
作为一个在春季工作的人
creation many you know for many
创造很多你知道很多
different years and you know talked
不同的年份，你知道说话
about it for much of the last decade I
在过去十年的大部分时间里
love spring irrigation so the DSL to me
爱春季灌溉，所以DSL给我
that is a really big deal and I don't
那是很重要的事情，我不会
think it gets enough time in the Sun so
认为它在阳光下有足够的时间，所以
we're going to talk about it we're going
我们要谈论它，我们要
to build an application today in terms
今天就构建一个应用程序而言
of that integration so let's build our
整合的基础，让我们构建我们的
first integration okay when I say what
我说什么的时候第一次整合好
I'm going to do is I'm going to build an
我要做的是建立一个
intuition that looks for data in a
在一个数据中寻找数据的直觉
directory so I'm going to build an
目录，所以我要建立一个
integration flow I'm going to call it
集成流程我将其称为
files right and the directory the
文件权和目录
directory full of information I'll just
目录，我将只提供信息
call it the input directory or I'll
称它为输入目录，否则我将
default to a a hard-coded paths here my
默认为这里我的硬编码路径
desktop in directory we'll call it file
目录中的桌面，我们将其称为文件
in ok so that'll be just Java IO file
好的，那将只是Java IO文件
and I'll use a spring property
我将使用spring属性
placeholder resolution to to make that
占位符分辨率，以使
value real and I'll use the dlci DSL
价值真实，我将使用dlci DSL
here I'm going to say whenever there's a
在这里我要说的是
new record coming in from something in
来自某物的新记录
this case I need to provide an inbound
这种情况下，我需要提供入站
adapter right that's the the the the
适配器的权利是
genesis of a messaging flow I'm going to
我要去的消息流的起源
respond I'm going to kick off this
回应，我将开始这个
processing flow if there's a message
有消息时的处理流程
that comes from this in-band adapter so
来自此带内适配器的
the embedded Apter is going to be the
嵌入式Apter将成为
ftp adapter so I need to bring in spring
ftp适配器，所以我需要带弹簧
integration FTP and there you can see
集成FTP，在那里您可以看到
there are a good many other modules here
这里还有很多其他模块
and then of course there are many more
然后当然还有更多
besides that are in the open source
除了开源
world that aren't included in spring
春天没有的世界
location itself so I'll say files dot
位置本身，所以我会说文件点
inbound adapter and what I want to do is
入站适配器，我想做的是
I want to I want to monitor the in
我要监视
directory very good and I don't need to
目录非常好，我不需要
provide a comparator so I'll leave it as
提供一个比较器，所以我将其保留为
is and I'm going to specify if you think
是，我要指定您是否认为
I'm going to say that I want to Auto
我要说的是我要自动
create the directory if it doesn't exist
创建目录（如果不存在）
absolutely I want to prevent duplicates
绝对我想防止重复
fair enough
很公平
and that'll be I think that'd be enough
我认为那就足够了
now what I want to do is I want to
现在我想做的是
transform it and we'll come back to what
改变它，我们会回到什么
I'm going to do with this later but for
我稍后会处理这个
now I'm going to create a I'm going to
现在我要创建一个
tell it to use this transformer
告诉它使用这个变压器
the contract for a transformer is
变压器的合同是
actually pretty straightforward right
其实很简单
it's a generic transformer we're going
这是我们要使用的通用变压器
to take the payload of type file in and
将类型文件的有效负载
we're going to send a string out and we
我们将发送一个字符串，我们
must implement that contract so there is
必须执行该合同，所以有
this right and that actually can be a
这项权利，实际上可以是
lambda right so that's a natural fit for
lambda对，因此很自然
lambda if we want we just need to
lambda如果我们想要我们只需要
specify this and then we can get rid of
指定这个，然后我们可以摆脱
all that right that gets much much
可以带来很多好处的所有权利
cleaner oops okay and then I want to I
清洁工哎呀，然后我要我
want to send it out so I'll handle the
要发送出去，所以我会处理
results with an adapter another adapter
一个适配器的结果另一个适配器
and in this case what I'm going to do is
在这种情况下，我要做的是
I'm going to send it to an FTP server so
我将其发送到FTP服务器
outbound adapter and I can't this
出站适配器，我不能
doesn't you know it doesn't work quite
你不知道那是行不通的吗
like this there's actually a very
像这样，实际上有一个非常
convenient interface that's expected
预期的便捷界面
here called a function that takes an
这里称为需要一个
adapters object and a message hand
适配器对象和消息手
respec so if we just provide this lambda
重新指定，以便我们是否仅提供此lambda
we can then use the adapters method here
然后我们可以在这里使用适配器方法
to to construct our flow here and it
在这里建立我们的流程
took expect it's expecting a FTP session
接受了期望它期待一个FTP会话
factory now I happen to have as I say a
我说我现在有一家工厂
FTP server running on my um on my
在我的um上运行的FTP服务器
machine
机
so we'll just create a simple session
所以我们只创建一个简单的会话
factory here that works for FTP files
适用于FTP文件的工厂
okay and it looks like I don't have the
好吧，看来我没有
type on the class path for that so let's
为此，请在类路径上输入
bring in spring integration FTP very
带来春季整合FTP
good and FTP file I guess that'll be
好的FTP文件，我想那是
enough let me see we want the default
足以让我看到我们想要默认值
FTP session factory right so save
FTP会话工厂正确，所以保存
ourselves from pain there we're going to
自己从痛苦中我们将要
say like this and I'm going to set the
这样说，我将设置
port equal to 21 21 you know the right
端口等于21 21你知道正确的
thing to do here by the way is to to use
顺便说一句在这里要做的就是使用
property so I should say you know FTP
属性，所以我应该说您知道FTP
port 21 21 into port
端口21 21进入端口
I want a username and I'll just provide
我想要一个用户名，我只提供
some default values here so the username
一些默认值，因此用户名
will be J long default rather and I'll
将会是J long的默认值，而我会
use a password so I'll say ftp password
使用密码，所以我会说ftp密码
otherwise the the password we spring
否则我们输入密码
there we go and and then we can just
我们去那里，然后我们就可以
configure I have to be session factory
配置我必须是会话工厂
with these defaults so we'll say FTP
这些默认值，所以我们将说FTP
session factory password close PW and
会话工厂密码关闭PW和
we'll say FTP that set username equals
我们说设置用户名等于的FTP
user name and that I think won't do so
用户名，我认为不会这样做
we'll just return that as as we done it
我们会像完成操作一样将其返回
and we as we've configured it and now
我们已经配置好了，现在
you can use the same code you just need
您可以使用只需要的相同代码
to provide properties via - T arguments
通过-T参数提供属性
or in the application uh properties or
或在应用程序中呃属性或
something let's start with FTP dot etc
让我们从FTP点开始
so we've done this now we've we just
所以我们现在已经完成了
need to tell spring to inject that being
需要告诉春天注入
here as a collaborating object so we'll
这里作为合作对象，所以我们将
we'll specify want the FTP session
我们将指定想要FTP会话
factory or the default FTP session
工厂或默认的FTP会话
factory here there we go and what's
工厂在这里，我们去了，什么
going to happen what's going to happen
将会发生的事情
is that we're going to run this adapter
是我们要运行此适配器
and it's going to it's going to need to
这将需要
generate a a file for us right it's
为我们生成一个文件
going to look it's going to try and
去看看它会尝试和
create the file for us and so we need to
为我们创建文件，所以我们需要
give it a way to do that and and I'm
给它一种方法去做，而我
gonna skip ahead here I'm going to go
要跳过这里我要去
ahead and create a temporary I'm going
继续并创建一个临时的
to I'm sorry I'm going to go ahead and
对不起，我要继续前进，
create a remote directory a remote
创建一个远程目录
directory a file name I'm trying to look
目录我要查找的文件名
for looking for the implementation file
用于查找实施文件
name expression generator file name
名称表达式生成器文件名
generator there we go we're going to
发电机，我们要去
provide a new file name generator and
提供一个新的文件名生成器并
our file name generator is gonna be
我们的文件名生成器将是
based on the head room so we're going to
根据头部空间，我们将
we're going to look at the incoming
我们将看看传入的
message right the spring integration
消息正确的春季整合
message I'm going to extract from the
我将从中提取的消息
message the
留言
header called the file name right so
标头叫做正确的文件名
we'll have the file name here and I'll
我们在这里有文件名，我将
let extract this and also return it as a
让我们将其提取出来并作为
value here and I'll say that I want to
珍惜这里，我会说我想
get the value string file name equals
获取值字符串文件名等于
string class cast Oh donar and all a
弦类演员哦，唐纳德和所有
return file name dot and what we're
返回文件名点和我们
going to do here my friends is we're
要在这里做我的朋友是我们
going to take the incoming files which
将要接收传入的文件
should be images right and in my case
应该是正确的图像，就我而言
I'm expecting images and we're going to
我期待图像，我们将
split the data we're going to we're
拆分我们要去的数据
going to process the data and turn it
要处理数据并打开它
into it and ask you our representation
并问你我们的代表
of that image so it'll be a it'll be a
该图像的所以它将是一个
text file so what I'm going to do is I'm
文本文件，所以我要做的是
going to split the the incoming file
将拆分传入的文件
name using a regular expression on the
使用正则表达式命名
period right there and then I'll say I
期间，然后我会说我
want to use the the first part of the of
想要使用的第一部分
the name and then I'll just rename it to
名称，然后我将其重命名为
dot txt okay so if it if it's dot jpg
点txt可以，如果是点jpg
then we'll if it's food at jpg well then
那我们就把它当成jpg的食物吧
we should name it on the file system in
我们应该在文件系统中将其命名为
the FTP server we'll name it
FTP服务器，我们将其命名为
food at txt instead okay so there we are
食物在txt而不是好的，所以我们在那里
this is a I wonder if this is a good
这是我不知道这是否很好
lambda candidate there we are
lambda候选人，我们在那里
yep looks nice so we can leave that and
是的看起来不错，所以我们可以离开
we don't need this either there we go
我们也不需要这个
that's cleaner so I think okay that's a
那比较干净，所以我认为那是
that's not bad right we've got a an
不错，我们有一个
adapter there and we finally need to
适配器在那里，我们最终需要
return the data now we do have to handle
现在返回数据，我们必须处理
this this transformation right and this
这个改造权和这个
is actually you know something maybe you
其实你知道一些也许你
would do in a separate expression maybe
可能会在一个单独的表达式中做
extract it out here and write the code
将其提取出来并编写代码
separately heck you could even put it in
单独地你甚至可以把它放进去
separate class and then more properly
单独上课，然后更适当
unit test it but for our purposes it
对其进行单元测试，但出于我们的目的
suffice is just just to do the code in
足够只是在执行代码
place so what we're going to do is we're
的地方，所以我们要做的是
going to take the data that's coming in
将要接收的数据
the file and we're going to create an
该文件，我们将创建一个
image banner so I'm going to say that I
图片横幅，所以我要说的是
want to create an image banner
要创建图像横幅
of it this is a new feature in spring
这是春天的新功能
1.4 it's all the rage it's certainly the
1.4这是所有的愤怒，当然是
most important thing that's ever
有史以来最重要的事情
happened to spring is the ability to to
春天发生的能力是
to turn images into ASCII art work
将图像转换为ASCII艺术品
automatically thank you to community
自动向社区表示感谢
member Craig perks and then I'll bring
成员克雷格（Craig）振作，然后我带
in the source there okay that's our
在源代码中，好吧，这是我们的
image banner and I'm going to write the
图片横幅，我要写
image banner out I'm going to print it
图片横幅出来，我要打印它
out so I need the environment there I
所以我需要那里的环境
can see that that's a requirement
可以看到这是必要条件
this is the spring environment
这是春天的环境
abstraction so I'll inject that there
抽象，所以我将其注入
and I need also a a class it doesn't
而且我还需要一个不需要的课程
really matter which one is just for
真正重要的是哪一个只适合
class loading and then I need a print
类加载，然后我需要打印
stream all right so I'm going to take
可以串流，所以我要
I'm going to say print stream PS will
我要说的是印刷流PS
equal new print stream and what you know
等于新的打印流和您所知道的
it when it was as with all things in I
就像我所有的一切一样
oh I want this to be automatically
哦，我希望这是自动的
closed at the end of the scope of its
在其范围的末尾关闭
usage so I'm going to wrap it the auto
用法，所以我要自动包装
closable sort of block introduced in
引入了可封闭的块
Java 7 my print stream needs a byte
Java 7我的打印流需要一个字节
array output
数组输出
you know I need an output stream so I'm
你知道我需要一个输出流，所以我
going to create a byte array output
将创建一个字节数组输出
stream like this okay and will will uh
这样好吧，会吧
whoops byte array output stream there we
哎呀字节数组输出流在那里
are and I need to handle this exception
是，我需要处理这个例外
that I've been invited into my world
我被邀请进入我的世界
here so there we are will say reflection
在这里，所以我们会说反思
utils dot we throw method we throw one
utils点我们抛出方法我们抛出一个
time exception II and now we'll pass
时间例外II，现在我们将通过
that byte array output stream to our
该字节数组输出流到我们
print stream which will then pass to
打印流，然后将传递给
this okay and once that's done I can say
好的，一旦完成，我可以说
byte array output stream dot two byte
字节数组输出流点两个字节
array and all the create a string
数组和所有创建一个字符串
you know banner text equals new string
你知道横幅文字等于新字符串
like that and we'll return the banner
这样，我们将返回横幅
text that wave worked so hard on so
如此努力的文字
we'll now we have our results we can
我们现在将获得我们的结果，我们可以
just in line in us both that seemed easy
就在我们身上，这似乎都很容易
enough and we're going to use that
足够，我们将使用它
transformer here so that's already been
变压器在这里，所以已经
plugged in right it says transform and
插入正确，上面写着transform and
in mind you I could have done all sorts
请记住，我本来可以做各种各样的事情
of other things here as well right I
还有这里的其他事情
showed you the the transformation I
向您展示了我的转型
chose your handle how to do handles and
选择你的手柄如何做手柄，
so on but I could split it I could do a
依此类推，但我可以将其拆分，
claim check I could do it you know I can
索赔支票我可以做到，你知道我可以
rich the data I could filter it and you
丰富的数据，我可以过滤它，你
know resequencing do also do cuz custom
知道重新排序也可以做cuz custom
routing to to other kinds of flows and
路由到其他类型的流，并
so on but this is I think a very very
等等，但这是我认为非常非常
simple example of what we're trying to
我们正在尝试的简单示例
do so let's go ahead and leave it as is
这样做，让我们继续并保持原样
as we have it right now now if this
因为我们现在就拥有它
works we should see the data we should
工作，我们应该看到我们应该得到的数据
see any input jpg file automatically
自动查看任何输入的jpg文件
appear as a resulting file in the FTP
在FTP中显示为结果文件
server so let's let's um again let's
服务器，让我们再次来吧，让我们
ensure that no matter what the nature of
确保无论什么性质
the file that it only accepts that the
该文件仅接受
you know the flow only works for for jpg
您知道该流程仅适用于jpg
file so we're going to go ahead and
文件，所以我们要继续
further customize our our pattern here
在这里进一步自定义我们的模式
the the thing that we're willing to
我们愿意做的事情
accept and so I suppose I suppose we
接受，所以我想我想我们
could just try this that might work
可以尝试这个可能会起作用
let's see if that works okay so it's
让我们看看是否可以，所以
probably ant path expression we can
也许我们可以蚂蚁路径表达
confirm as much by looking at this and
通过查看确认尽可能多
it says the pattern and new simple
它说的模式和新的简单
pattern file list filter and the filter
模式文件列表过滤器和过滤器
it's an N style and style path
这是一个N样式和样式路径
expression so yeah that should be that
表达，是的，应该是这样
should be find right just as and style
应该和风格一样正确找到
asterisk dot jpg okay good so now we
星号点jpg好，所以现在我们
have a integration flow that'll listen
有一个可以听的整合流程
for data here transform the incoming
对于这里的数据转换传入
file using our file to string generic
文件，使用我们的文件将字符串通用
transformer and then and then route the
变压器，然后路由
resulting string outside now the last
现在最后一个之外的结果字符串
thing that we need to do is we need to
我们需要做的是
make sure that that header that has the
确保具有
file name in it is perpetuated so
其中的文件名是永久的，因此
instead of just sending a string we're
而不只是发送一个字符串，我们
going to we're going to send a a message
去我们要发送一条消息
of string right this is a the wrapper
正确的字符串，这是一个包装器
object
宾语
spring framework itself expects and we
Spring Framework本身期望，我们
will we will oblige right so I'm going
我们会义务正确吗，我要走了
to say message builder and this is the
说消息生成器，这是
this is actually a spring framework ISM
这实际上是一个Spring框架ISM
we're going to build a custom envelope
我们将建立一个自定义信封
object called a message I'm going to
对象，我要去的消息
build it but before we build it we want
建立它，但是在我们建立它之前，我们想要
to set a header so we're going to set
设置标题，所以我们要设置
the header to be the file name itself
标头是文件名本身
and the file name will be of course the
文件名当然是
the incoming file source so get absolute
传入的文件源，因此获取绝对值
file dot get name okay so there's that
文件点获取名称好，所以有
and there we go there's our simple flow
然后我们开始进行简单的流程
so that way the downstream component
这样下游组件
that is to say our our outbound ftp
也就是说我们的出站ftp
adapter will be able to take the
适配器将能够
incoming file header and and split it
传入文件头并将其拆分
successfully right otherwise that header
成功，否则该标头
might not be there so this is a good
可能不在那里，所以这很好
chance to look at how spring you know
有机会看看你知道春天如何
what's happening underneath the hood
引擎盖下发生了什么
even though our components are written
即使我们的组件是书面的
in terms of strings and files and so on
在字符串和文件等方面
what's really happening is spring is
真正发生的是春天是
perpetuating message objects which have
使具有以下内容的消息对象永久存在
payloads and that's why these components
有效载荷，这就是为什么这些组件
work is because all these components
工作是因为所有这些组成部分
really care about at the very lowest
真的很在乎
levels is or they care about untyped you
水平是或他们关心未输入您的信息
know generic objects of type message
知道消息类型的通用对象
which have payloads and and headers
有有效载荷和头
which which in turn are keys and values
依次是键和值
so there's no there's no reason that
所以没有任何理由
they shouldn't work together right there
他们不应该在那里一起工作
they're meant to work together even if
他们注定要一起工作，即使
the payloads and so on are different and
有效载荷等等是不同的，
you can actually switch out the behavior
您实际上可以切换行为
by switching out the components upstream
通过关闭上游组件
or downstream right so let's go ahead
还是下游，所以让我们继续吧
and see if this works okay that should
看看是否可行，应该
be a very simple example and this will
是一个非常简单的例子，这将
be our spring integration flow let me go
是我们的春季整合流程，让我走吧
to my desktop here let me go to my
到我的桌面上，让我进入
desktop here
桌面在这里
now remove the input directory and will
现在删除输入目录，将
we see in the FTPS directory and the FTP
我们在FTPS目录和FTP
server that I have nothing there yet
服务器，我什么都没有
right now so I'm gonna you know I'm
现在我要你知道我是
going to hopefully see txt files once
希望一次看到txt文件
we've added images to the in directory
我们已经将图片添加到了in目录中
so let's go ahead and try this we'll go
因此，让我们继续尝试，我们将继续
ahead and spin this up everything
向前并旋转一切
everything should go to plan hopefully
一切都应该按计划进行
but a I've said that before so we'll see
但是我之前已经说过，所以我们会看到
aha so learning moment tried i i didn't
啊哈，所以学习的时候尝试了二没有
control i didn't configure and a polar
控制我没有配置和极地
right i didn't control a configure polar
对，我没有控制极性配置
for my inbound adapter now this makes
对于我的入站适配器，这使得
sense so remember spring integration is
所以记得弹簧整合是
going to let let us write code as though
让我们像那样编写代码
the messages will come as an event right
消息将作为事件而来
the downstream components don't need to
下游组件不需要
care about where these these incoming
关心这些这些传入的地方
messages come right so for example the
消息正确，例如
transform component here this filed a
转换组件在这里提交了
string generic component that has no
没有的字符串通用组件
idea where this incoming file comes from
这个传入文件来自哪里的想法
but we know upstream you know or we know
但我们知道你知道还是我们知道
upstream that the the message comes from
消息来自上游
this inbound adapter the inbound adapter
此入站适配器入站适配器
is going to respond to new messages and
将要响应新消息，并且
it does this by pulling the file system
它通过拉文件系统来做到这一点
that is to say it scans the file system
也就是说它扫描文件系统
at a period at an interval so we need to
每隔一段时间，我们需要
configure that interval we need to
配置该间隔，我们需要
configure you know how often it should
配置您知道应该多久一次
do that but not all systems have this
这样做，但并非所有系统都具有此功能
requirement right not all systems are
要求权不是所有系统都
unable to pull themselves right for so
不能为此而正确
for example IMAP idle IMAP idle has a
例如IMAP空闲IMAP空闲有一个
way to do push notifications you don't
推送通知的方式
need to constantly interrogate it you
需要不断审问你
can just listen asynchronously and be
可以异步听
told of when the message is there
被告知消息何时存在
similarly you know your message queues
同样，您知道您的消息队列
for example rabbitmq and then most Jamis
例如rabbitmq，然后是大多数贾米斯
and Jamis brokers and so on or have a
和Jamis经纪人等等，或者
way of doing the same thing so so spring
春天做同样的事情的方式
negation has this idea of a polar for
否定的想法是极地
those systems that don't have this idea
那些没有这个主意的系统
so that from our perspective we can
这样，从我们的角度来看，我们可以
write code as though the message will
编写代码，就像消息将
get delivered asynchronously and it
异步交付
doesn't matter if the the original
原来的没关系
system actually supports it right we'll
系统实际上支持它，我们会
make it work one by another so I'm going
让它一个接一个地工作，所以我要
to say that I want to pull
说我想拉
all the the directory every second 1000
每秒钟所有目录1000
milliseconds and let's go ahead and
毫秒，让我们继续前进，
restart this here okay good stuff so
在这里重启这个好东西，所以
those are our simple integration flow
这些是我们简单的集成流程
let's go ahead and try this out so I'm
让我们继续尝试一下，这样我
going to copy the Google logo here into
将此处的Google徽标复制到
the input directory and we see that it
输入目录，我们看到它
failed utterly and and completely and
彻底彻底失败
the remote directory expression AHA I
远程目录表达式AHA I
forgot to specify where I want the
忘记指定我想要的位置
incoming you know files to be to be
传入您知道的文件是
written so I'm going to call this what
写的，所以我要称它为
did I say what was that last directory
我是否说过最后一个目录是什么
uploads okay
可以上传
now that message that file is still
现在，该文件仍然存在的消息
resident in the in the directory so as
驻留在目录中，以便
soon as it started up again it noticed
再次启动时，它注意到
it and it you know successfully create
它，你知道成功创建
the message and it sent the message
消息，它发送了消息
through the processing chain so users
通过处理链，使用户
jail on desktop in google jpg was
谷歌jpg桌面上的监狱是
created and then finally down here in
创建，然后终于在这里
the FTP session logic we see file has
我们看到文件的FTP会话逻辑
been successfully transferred to uploads
已成功转移到上传
Google dot txt dot writing and then
谷歌点txt点写作然后
finally it was renamed to upload stat
最终它被重命名为上传统计信息
Google txt so here we already get some
Google txt，所以在这里我们已经得到了一些
benefit you can see that this is a the
好处，你可以看到这是一个
spring innovation outbound FTP adapter
Spring Innovation出站FTP适配器
is doing something very smart you see
在做一些非常聪明的事情
there may be yet there may be further
可能还有可能
other systems even others even more
其他系统甚至其他系统
systems downstream that are waiting for
正在等待的下游系统
this file and those systems downstream
该文件以及下游的那些系统
may may be doing the same thing maybe
可能正在做同样的事情，也许
they're pulling the FTP server as the
他们将FTP服务器作为
you know that's how they're staging
你知道那是他们分期的方式
they're waiting 50 P server to arrive on
他们正在等待50 P服务器到达
the F T they're waiting for the file to
他们正在等待文件的FT
arrive on the FTP server and then they
到达FTP服务器，然后他们
want to process it when it's there well
想在合适的地方进行处理
if we're uploading a file and that file
如果我们正在上传文件和该文件
is named as as the downtube systems are
被命名为下导管系统
expecting it to be named then those
期望它被命名，然后那些
downstream systems may observe them they
下游系统可能会观察到它们
notice them or perceive them there and
注意到他们或在那里感知他们
just start downloading them so that they
刚开始下载它们，以便他们
can start processing them even though we
可以开始处理它们，即使我们
haven't finished uploading them so what
还没有上传完，怎么办
we've done here is spring negations
我们在这里做的是春季否定
outbound adapter uploads it using a
出站适配器使用
different name it's uh fixes it with dot
它是不同的名称，用点号将其修复
writing and so hopefully the downstream
写作，所以希望下游
systems mask is such that it doesn't
系统掩码是这样的
look for a file ending with dot writing
寻找以点写结尾的文件
right and then when it's finally all
对，然后当一切都结束时
uploaded we just rename it so then it's
上传我们只是重命名它，然后
a sort of a pseudo atomic or at least
一种伪原子或至少
very very quick and it works ok so there
非常非常快，效果很好，所以在那里
we go so that worked we actually have
我们去，以便我们实际上有工作
now an an ASCII art work file in the in
现在是一个ASCII艺术品文件
the desktop here so ftp WS uploads
此处的桌面，以便ftp WS上传
there's our Google logo and a Scout work
有我们的Google徽标和侦察员作品
you can't really see it here I wonder if
你真的不能在这里看到它，我想知道
I can cat it all right cat here we are
我可以在这里照顾好猫
there we are there's our ask our work on
那里我们在问我们的工作
the console it's a thing of beauty I
控制台这是一件美丽的事，我
think you'll agree now one one thing you
想你现在会同意一件事
may be wondering is well how do I reuse
可能想知道如何重新使用
dysfunctionality how do i I mean I've
功能失调，我该怎么办？
done all this logic how do i how do i
完成了所有这些逻辑后，我该怎么办
encapsulate it maybe I want to take
封装它也许我想拿
advantage of all the inbound file
所有入站文件的优势
monitoring and the the a secure
监控和安全
transformation but maybe I want to have
转型，但也许我想拥有
two different terminus from my from my
与我不同的两个终点
resulting message maybe I want to send
结果消息也许我想发送
it out to an FTP server and send it as a
将其发送到FTP服务器并将其作为
message to a rabbitmq broker and so here
给rabbitmq经纪人的消息等等
again spring negation is isn't is a
再次春天否定是不是
great fit right so what we're doing here
非常合适，所以我们在这里做什么
is were implicitly sending data from one
是从一个隐式发送数据
component the embedded after to the
组件嵌入到
transformer to the to the outbound
变压器到出站
adapter and we're not explicitly
适配器，我们没有明确
describing the flow of that message
描述该消息的流向
between components it's just assumed for
在组件之间只是假设
us in spring to Beijing we call this a
我们春天到北京，我们称之为
chained flow right but we can make that
链流正确，但我们可以做到
conveyance explicit and this is actually
明确的运输方式，这实际上是
to our benefit there's this notion of a
对我们有利的是
message channel a message channel and
消息通道消息通道和
spring integration refers to a named
春季整合是指一个命名
conduit it's a pipe through through
导管是一条穿过的管道
which message is passed and we can use
传递哪个消息，我们可以使用
channels to stage the output of one flow
用于分流一个流的输出的通道
for delivery to another flow so let's go
交付给另一个流程，所以我们开始吧
ahead and break this apart let's go
向前并打破这一点，让我们开始吧
ahead and move the processing for the
向前移动处理
FTP to another flow and then we'll add
FTP到另一个流，然后我们将添加
another flow still so that you know
另一股流仍然，所以你知道
we're going to have the the original
我们将拥有原始的
flow it'll it'll send a message on a
流它会在
channel and we'll have two different
频道，我们将有两个不同的频道
consumers at the end of that channel the
该渠道末端的消费者
other side of that channel that will
该通道的另一侧
process it right so we're going to go
处理正确，所以我们要走了
ahead and now build a channel will say
前进，现在建立一个渠道会说
message channel and I'm going to call
信息频道，我要打电话
this the you know what I'm going to call
这你知道我要打电话
this via the file processors I guess or
通过我猜的文件处理器
ASCII processors that makes more sense
更加有意义的ASCII处理器
doesn't it so we'll call these the ASCII
不是吗，所以我们将其称为ASCII
processors and we're just going to turn
处理器，我们将转向
a message channel and again a message
一个消息通道，再一个消息
channel has no no implied functionality
通道没有任何隐含功能
by default right it's just a named
默认情况下，它只是一个命名
conduit it's like a Java util Q in the
就像一个Java util Q
common case right so I'm going to build
正确的案例，所以我要建立
a a publish/subscribe channel and here
一个发布/订阅频道，这里
we go we're going to go ahead and build
我们走，我们要继续前进，并建立
it like that and we're going to use that
这样，我们将使用它
channel to to send this data out so
发送此数据的渠道
instead of
代替
saying handle with adapter I'll cut that
说带适配器的手柄，我会切
out and I'll say handle or sorry channel
出来，我会说句“不好意思”或“抱歉”的频道
this dot ascii processors so now it's
这个点ascii处理器，所以现在
being sent on the channel where we don't
被发送到我们不接收的频道
know but we don't care either right we
知道，但我们也不在乎我们
just noticed it's some other downstream
只是注意到这是其他下游
component will respond to it so now
组件将对此做出响应，所以现在
let's go ahead and reinstate the ftp
让我们继续并恢复ftp
flow we're going to say FTP and we will
流程，我们要说FTP，我们将
return an integration flow dot from this
从中返回积分流点
dot ASCII processors and we'll you know
点ASCII处理器，我们会知道
same basic thing here except we're
除了我们
taking the data from our incoming
从传入的数据中获取数据
channel so now our code becomes a little
渠道，所以现在我们的代码变得有点
bit more modular to write so we get we
更具模块化的编写方式，因此我们可以
get benefits by using channels now we
现在通过使用渠道获得收益
can reason and we can test out sub
可以推理，我们可以测试子
sections of the flow of the processing
部分流程的处理
flow without having to test everything
流动而不必测试所有内容
right we can in in you in isolation we
对，我们可以孤立地进入您
can see that this flow for sending a
可以看到此流程用于发送
message to the ftp server works in fact
消息到ftp服务器实际上起作用
you could inject just this channel
您可以只注入这个频道
itself into your code and send a message
本身进入您的代码并发送消息
into that channel you don't have to have
进入该频道，您不必
a you know a spring integration
你知道弹簧整合
component for example so that in a you
例如组件，以便在您
know if you did that you would see the
知道你是否这样做，你会看到
message go through the ftp logic until
消息通过ftp逻辑直到
you got that correct until it was
你得到了正确的，直到
working the way you expected for example
以您期望的方式工作，例如
okay so now i've decoupled them now what
好吧，现在我已经将它们解耦了
else can i do i want to go ahead and
否则我可以继续吗
send the message out on to AMQP so at
发送消息到AMQP，以便
this point I've got actually two
这一点我实际上有两个
different concerns don't die I've got
我有不同的担忧不会消失
the FTP configuration and I've got the
FTP配置，我已经
amqp RabbitMQ configuration so let's go
amqp RabbitMQ配置，让我们开始吧
ahead and kind of coordinating off from
领先和协调从
each other there we go this is a nested
彼此那里我们去这是一个嵌套
configuration class it when spring sees
弹簧看到时的配置类
that it'll evaluate just like any other
它会像其他任何东西一样评估
configuration class and we are going to
配置类，我们将要
go ahead and now do the same thing for
继续，现在做同样的事情
AMQP will say configuration public
AMQP将说配置公开
static class mq p configuration and what
静态类mq p配置以及什么
are we going to do we're going to define
我们要做的是定义
the the middleware the infrastructure
中间件基础架构
that's spring aim to p and spring
那是p和春天的春天
integration need
整合需求
to talk to to talk to mqp so I need to
与mqp交谈，所以我需要
bring in here the spring integration mqp
在这里引入春季集成mqp
dependency and we need to define we need
依赖，我们需要定义我们需要的
to define the the infrastructure the the
定义基础架构
objects the structures on the rabbitmq
反对Rabbitmq上的结构
broker and I happen to have rabbitmq
经纪人和我碰巧有rabbitmq
running on my machine right now so it's
现在在我的机器上运行，所以
already on the same machine I don't need
已经在我不需要的同一台机器上
to to do anything else to it I just no I
去做别的事情我只是不我
just it's running locally and by virtue
只是在本地运行并凭借
of the fact that I've brought in spring
我在春天带来的事实
boots starter AMQP I will get and I will
我会得到的靴子启动器AMQP
get a connection factory that's pointing
得到一个指向的连接工厂
to local host so that's the default
到本地主机，所以这是默认设置
values naturally I could go to
我自然可以去看重
application our properties and say
应用我们的属性并说
spring rabbitmq and specify any number
spring Rabbitmq并指定任何数字
these are properties to to specify how
这些是用于指定如何使用的属性
to find the broker but for our purposes
寻找经纪人，但出于我们的目的
it is fine as is I'm going to create a
很好，因为我要创建一个
some of these server-side infrastructure
其中一些服务器端基础架构
that's required so in spring sorry in
这是必需的，所以在春天对不起
rabbitmq you have this idea of a broker
rabbitmq你有经纪人的想法
and the broker accepts messages at
经纪人在接受消息
something called an exchange which is
所谓的交流是
sort of like a door or a gate the
有点像一扇门或一扇门
exchange then does routing it sends the
交换然后路由它发送
message to some sort of queue so there
消息发送到某种队列，所以在那里
are different kinds of exchanges and if
是不同类型的交流，如果
you want to do pub/sub you know
你想做发布/订阅你知道的
broadcast kind of a public communication
广播形式的公共传播
there's a in exchange for that if you
如果你有一个交换
want to do direct communication there's
想要直接沟通
an exchange exchange for that if you
交换交换，如果你
want to do hierarchical topics which is
想做分层主题
a feature that you can't really get in
您无法真正使用的功能
standard JMS for example there's an
例如，标准的JMS
exchange for that exchange is actually
交换实际上是交换
used also as a way of doing a federation
也用作联盟的一种方式
right you can do replication from you
对的你可以从你那里复制
know active active kind of replication
知道主动主动复制的种类
from one node to another and they're
从一个节点到另一个节点
also they're also how random queue
他们也是随机队列
supports talking to other protocols
支持与其他协议通话
right if you want to send a message to
如果您想发送消息到
RabbitMQ you send it to an exchange and
您将RabbitMQ发送到交易所，
it can it can then rewrite it for you
它可以为您重写它吗
and send it out over as a XMPP for
并将其作为XMPP发送出去
example or something like this right so
例子或类似的东西，所以
so you have a lot of flexibility in this
所以你在这方面有很大的灵活性
exchange construct it adds the ability
交换构造它增加了能力
to do routing in the broker itself right
在代理本身中进行路由
which is not something you get in the
那不是你得到的
very simplistic JMS model and JMS it's a
非常简单的JMS模型和JMS
message goes to a destination and then
信息到达目的地，然后
the consumer listens on the Destiny
消费者聆听命运
there's no intermediary so you're
没有中介，所以你
coupled there right the those things can
再加上那些东西可以
never change so let's go ahead and let's
永不改变，让我们继续前进，让我们
define the the relevant bits here so we
在这里定义相关的位，所以我们
care about the exchange sure right we
关心交流，确定我们正确
need a spring AMQP exchange
需要春季AMQP交换
okay so we'll use the exchange builder
好吧，我们将使用交易所生成器
in spring AMQP and we'll use a direct
在春季AMQP，我们将使用直接
exchange and you know the exchange here
交流，你知道这里的交流
is going to called ASCII well everything
一切都会被称为ASCII
will be ASCII so okay that'll be the
将是ASCII，所以好的，它将是
name of the I want this to be durable
我希望它的名称持久
don't we all right okay we'll build that
难道我们会建立的吗
that means that the data will be it the
这意味着数据将是
exchange will be kept we want to send
交换将保留，我们要发送
the data that comes into the exchange
交换中的数据
through a to a queue right so we'll
通过一个到队列，所以我们将
create a queue here we'll say so we're
在这里创建一个队列，我们​​会说，
going to use the queue builder and we'll
将使用队列生成器，我们将
make this durable as well so we'll say Q
使它也耐用，所以我们说Q
giving it a name this dot s key dot
给它起一个点的名称
build okay there's that finding right we
建立好，找到正确的我们
need to build the binding here so we're
需要在这里建立绑定，所以我们
going to build the binding we'll say
要建立绑定，我们会说
return binding builder dot bind the X
返回绑定生成器点绑定X
the exchange to the Q you know like so
这样交换到你知道的Q
or bind the Q I suppose to the exchange
或将QI假设绑定到交易所
okay with a routing key and the routing
可以使用路由键和路由
key is a is the header that spring
关键是一个是春天的头
rabbim q will will use to to decide to
rabbim q将用来决定
determine which queue to send a message
确定发送消息的队列
right so the message is going to come
对，所以消息即将到来
into the exchange and rabbim q is gonna
进入交易所，rabbim q将
say okay well how do I know where to
说好吧，我怎么知道去哪里
send this and a common pattern is to use
发送这个，一个常见的模式是使用
a header a special magic header I'm well
一个头，一个特殊的魔术头，我很好
known header called routing key in
称为路由关键字的已知标头
select a traveling key in this case will
在这种情况下选择旅行钥匙
be that the
是因为
the message has the the writing team
消息有写作团队
will be the expression the ASCII right
将是ASCII右表达式
that's that'll be the name so I'm using
那就是名字，所以我正在使用
conventional musing engineered
传统的沉思工程
coincidence here so that everything
巧合在这里，让一切
lines up and now we need to build the
排队，现在我们需要建立
integration flow to support that right
集成流程以支持该权利
so I'm going to say in this case that
所以我要说的是
when data comes in I'll have another
当数据输入时，我会有另一个
integration flow mqp and we'll say
集成流程mqp，我们将说
integration flow dot from this dot to a
从该点到
skew processors and we'll say handle
倾斜的处理器，我们将说句柄
with adapter and we're going to do the
与适配器，我们将要做
same thing again except this time to nqp
除了这次对nqp再次相同
and the mqp bits is going to need a name
mqp位将需要一个名称
QP template right so we'll say a inject
QP模板正确，所以我们将注入
the AMQP template which is a
AMQP模板是
automatically provided for us by spring
春季自动为我们提供
boo try the auto configuration there is
嘘尝试自动配置
this and well the exchange name of
这以及很好的交换名称
course will be will be a ASCII so I
当然将是ASCII，所以我
guess we should make that value well
猜想我们应该很好地实现这一价值
even you know what this flow could
即使你知道这种流动会怎样
actually be local to that configuration
实际上在该配置本地
that's actually another really
这实际上是另一个
convenient side-effect of this sort of
这种方便的副作用
modeling ISM we get that although now of
建模ISM我们知道，尽管现在
course the the channel doesn't work so
当然，频道无法正常运作
maybe it's just better to flatten this
也许最好把它弄平
for now let's just flatten this
现在让我们把它弄平
configuration namespace I'm going to say
我要说的配置名称空间
that the the data what as it comes in
数据是什么
will be delivered to ASCII and the
将以ASCII格式传送，
routing key will be this ASCII okay so
路由密钥将是此ASCII格式，所以
there's our integration flow when it
当我们有整合流程时
comes in from this channel it's going to
从这个频道进来
be sent out on to the AMQP adapter we're
发送到我们正在使用的AMQP适配器上
just going to send it to that exchange
只是要发送到那个交易所
using this routing key okay so the you
使用这个路由键好吧，你
know it should work as expected it'll
知道它应该能按预期工作
get delivered to the queue and hopefully
被送到队列，并希望
something on the other side will be able
另一边的东西将能够
to to respond to it okay so let's go
回应它好吧，让我们开始吧
ahead and try this out now if everything
继续尝试，现在就尝试一下
goes to plan we should see the results
去计划，我们应该看到结果
in the RabbitMQ broker let me let's
在RabbitMQ经纪人中，让我
confirm by logging into rabbim queuing
通过登录rabbim队列进行确认
and clearing out whatever we've gotten
并清理我们得到的一切
there already so I've got three mess
已经在那里，所以我有三个烂摊子
Edge's let me just go ahead and purge it
Edge让我继续清除它
right now okay purge delete even since
现在就可以清除删除，即使
we want to start from zero and we'll go
我们想从零开始，然后我们去
ahead and restart
提前重启
ah seems I've already got it in the in
啊，看来我已经在里面了
the broker I've already got this
我已经有了这个经纪人
exchange and so on so I need to delete
交换等等，所以我需要删除
all of it so that my configuration that
所有这些，以便我的配置
I provide doesn't conflict with what's
我提供与什么不冲突
actually in practice in play right so
实际上在练习中是正确的，所以
queues
s列
there's gone exchanges gone go ahead and
交流已经过去了，
restart and let the the new
重新启动，让新
configuration override whatever I had
配置覆盖了我的一切
before cool so we saw that the file
之前很酷，所以我们看到了文件
still in the directory it so it's been
仍然在目录中，所以它已经
upload to the server it's replaced it
上载到服务器替换它
and now if we go to here we should see
现在，如果我们去这里，我们应该看到
ASCII there it is right there those are
ASCII那里就是那些
ASCII exchange let's see what's in the
ASCII交换让我们看看其中的内容
queue that's where the data is actually
队列实际上是数据所在的位置
stored after all and there's one message
毕竟存储了，只有一条信息
as yet to process this as yet processed
尚未处理
and so we can get them the message here
所以我们可以在这里给他们消息
by saying get message and there it is
通过说出获取消息，就可以了
and all of its glory the the ask out
和所有的荣耀
work for the Google message so our
为Google信息工作，因此我们的
Google logo rather so there we go we've
谷歌徽标，所以我们走了，我们已经
used spring abrasion and we've staged
使用了春季磨料，我们上演了
our processing through channels now this
现在我们通过渠道进行处理
channel concept is going to be very very
渠道概念将会非常非常
useful later on right so if you're using
稍后会很有用，所以如果您使用
spring framework itself you can use
您可以使用的Spring框架本身
channels to work with WebSockets right
与WebSockets配合使用的通道
and spring MVC yeah and if you're using
和春季MVC是的，如果您使用的是
spring Club stream then the channel
春天俱乐部流然后通道
becomes the sort of connective tissue
变成一种结缔组织
between messaging based micro services
基于消息的微服务之间
and we'll talk about this more I hope in
我希望在以后再讨论这个
further installments but a with that
进一步的分期付款但是
thanks very much and see you next time
非常感谢，下次见